>> Brian Holt: 我正在显示您，请使用回调。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So I was showing you,
you use callback.
这样做的方式也相对相同。
This works relatively the same way.
这有点不同我们在用它和一个叫
It's slightly different in that, we're
using it together with something called
备忘录的形式与使用备忘录的方式不同
memo, right here, which is different
than use memo, by the way.
这让他们把他们称为类似的事情
That's confusing that they call
them the similar thing, but
把想法分开
just separate the ideas.
如果你见过纯成分，那就是
If you've ever seen pure component,
which is a react construct for
类的性能。
performance for classes.
备忘录是为了履行职责，我随时在此解释。
Memo is that for functions, and
I'll explain that here momentarily.
>> Brian Holt: 在此，我具有回调组件，并且
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So here,
I have the callback component, and
我这里有一个时钟每隔一秒更新一次。
I have this clock here that's
updating every single second.
然后我就有个时间了
And then I have a time an account.
这是两种不同的状态。
These are two different pieces of state.
然后我在这里产生了一个影响这个时钟的作用。
And then I have an effect here
that moves this clock up.
就像我之前解释的那样
And just like I was explaining before,
the way the react
工作是每一个子代一次重新运行一次它的每一个子代。
works is that a rerun orders every all
of its children every single time.
这条路走得挺快的
Cuz that assumes that path is quite fast.
但是如果你有一个大的斐波纳契那就不再是真的了
However, if you have a big Fibonacci,
that's no longer true.
所以如果我在这儿
So if I get up here.
> > Brian Holt: 所以最多 38个。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So it's up to 38.
请注意，此情况仍在推进， 1:22:18 ，但是
Notice that this is still advancing,
1:22:18, but
请注意，最后一次重新呈现不会更改。
notice this last rerender is not changing.
这是最后一次重新呈现的时间。
So the last time that rerendered.
那就是那个时候，所以每次都不重新渲染。
Was that, that time, and so it's not
re-rendering this every single time.
否则这会死去
Otherwise, this would die,
因为它每次都在尝试计算 40 % 的斐波纳奇
because it would be trying to calculate
the Fibonacci of 40 every single time.
这对解决这里的问题有什么意义吗
Does that make sense of
what it's solving here?
让我们来谈谈它是如何运作的。
So let's talk about how it actually works.
所以在这里我有一个昂贵的计算组件
So down here, I have the expensive
computation component which actually does,
这部分组件就在那儿
this part of the component right there.
它有一个叫做计算的函数，它有一个叫做计数的函数。
And it has a function called compute,
and it has a function called count.
这就是通过的两个道具
So these are the two props
that are being passed into
昂贵的计算组件
expensive computation component.
Expensive computation component,
是备忘录中的一个组成部分这就是备忘录的意思
is a memo wised component which is
what this memo means right there.
>> Brian Holt: 备忘录的含义是，只要我的属性没有变化，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: What memo means is, as long
as none of my properties have changed,
别再跟我说了
don't re-render me.
因此，只要计算和计数相同，计算和计数。
So as long as compute and
count are the same, compute and count.
请不要再渲染我了
Please do not re-render me.
所以这才是能够继续下去的原因。
So that's why this is able to keep going.
而且它还在工作，而且它说，把这个单独留下。
And it's still working, and
it's saying, leave this one alone.
我们呼叫计算和计算
And we call compute and count right there,
否则，这将是每一次计算一次，这将是一场灾难。
otherwise this would be computing every
single time, and it would be a disaster.
我们这样做的方式
And the way we do that,
我们把这个备忘录和这个叫做 " 用回调" 的东西结合使用
is we use this memo in conjunction with
this thing here called useCallback.
useCallback 与 useMemo 几乎相同。
useCallback works almost
the same as useMemo.
但你在这里做的是给它一个功能，而你给它的依赖性
But what it's doing here is you give it a
function, and you give it dependencies of
您希望该函数在此情况下更新的频率，
how often you want that function
to update which in this case,
都是一样的功能对吧
it's always the same function, right?
所以这个斐波纳契永远都是一样的
So this Fibonacci is always
going to be the same, and
计数为，仅在计数更改时更新。
the count is,
it only updates when count changes.
我们本来可以这样做的我们本来可以这样做的
Now, we could have done this differently,
we could have structured this so
这不是什么问题
this wasn't a problem.
但注意， Fibonacci 是回调组件内部的变量。
But notice here that Fibonacci is
the variable inside of callback component.
所以如果我把它直接改变为斐波纳奇的话
So if I change this to be
just Fibonacci directly,
注意在这里它每次都在重新渲染
notice that this right here,
it's rerendering every single time.
因此，如果这一情况开始成为一个大数字， >> Brian Holt: 这个
So if this starts to become a big number,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This
会让人痛苦得很快
is gonna get really painful really fast.
> > Brian Holt: [LAUGH] 现在，它使我的浏览器实际上有点难以使用。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: [LAUGH] Now, it's making
my browser actually kind of hard to use.
[ LAUGH] >> Brian Holt: 您可以看到我
[LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You can see that I
连卷轴都画得不好
can't even scroll very well anymore.
好了别说了
Okay, stop it.
好吧我宁愿有个错误
Okay, I'd rather have an error.
> > Brian Holt: [LAUGH] 好，我们开始。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: [LAUGH] All right,
there we go.
我可能要在那之后刷新我的浏览器。
I might have to refresh my
browser after that one.
因为你每次都在重新定义斐波纳契
That's because what you're redefining
Fibonacci every single time, so
这种功能在技术上是每一次改变的
that function technically is
changing every single time.
这是新的斐波纳契函数
It's a new Fibonacci function.
这就是回调的用途。
So that's what use callback does.
就像，嘿，这没变，
It's like, hey, this isn't changing,
每次都给我同样的功能
give me back the same
function every single time.
>> Brian Holt: 有意义吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Make sense?
好的。
Okay.
>> Brian Holt: 再次，仅使用备忘录和
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Again, only use memo and
当您实际上已存在问题时，请使用备忘录和使用回调。
use memo and use callback when you
actually already have a problem.
不要先发制人地使用它们。
Do not preemptively use them.
我已经看到团队在任何地方都使用预先的组件和备忘录。
I've seen teams use pre-component and
memo everywhere.
简直一团糟
It's a mess.
相信我这种反应 99 次是 100次
Believe me, that react,
99 times out of 100,
从 1000 到 999 的 999 次，已足够快。
999 times out of 1000,
is fast enough as is.
它让你的代码不太容易出错
And it makes your code less prone to bugs
如果你不需要用这些东西的话
if you don't use those things
when you don't need them.